clearindices.net 2009-05-18

# Clear Indexes LLC

CLEAR INDEXES LLC ("Clear Indexes") values the privacy of our clients ("You," "Your," "User(s)") and places a high priority on safeguarding Your confidential information. The following privacy policy explains the procedures and policies Clear Indexes employs to protect Your confidential information when using [www.clearindexes.com](http://www.clearindexes.com/), [www.clearindexes](http://www.clearindexes/).net, [www.clearindices.com](http://www.clearindices.com/) or [www.clearindices.net](http://www.clearindices.net/) (the "Site"). 

**Use Of The Clear Indexes Site**

You may visit the Site and read about products and services of Clear Indexes, read our corporate information and get news about us without providing any personal information. 

**Information Collected By Clear Indexes  
**  
**_Personal information_**

Clear Indexes may collect personal information in order to provide You with access to advanced account features on the Site or affiliate sites. By providing any personal information to the Site or affiliate sites, all Users acknowledge that they fully understand and unambiguously consent to the collection and processing of such information in the United States. 

**Sharing of User Information**

Several different types of Users use the Site or affiliate sites: free Users, newsletter subscribers and asset management Clients. Unless express written permission is granted by specific Users, Clear Indexes will not share User Information with third parties. All Users are requested on a voluntary and/or sweepstake basis to participate in a survey. 

**_Non-personal information_**

Clear Indexes collects non-personal information in order to personalize Your experience on the Site, diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Site. Clear Indexes may analyze non-personal usage data and develop reports generated from the server's log files. Clear Indexes may use this information for marketing purposes and to enhance the Site's features and functionality. Clear Indexes does not share non-personal statistics with others outside of Clear Indexes or its affiliates. 

In order to administer the Site and enhance our Services, Clear Indexes collects and analyzes statistical non-personal information. This data may include: 

Additionally, the Site uses "cookies" during Your visit. "Cookies" are text files sent from our server and stored by Your web browser on Your computer's hard drive. Clear Indexes uses cookies to collect anonymous data which allows us to personalize Your experience with the Site. The cookies used during Your visit to the site can only be read by servers of Clear Indexes. Cookies will not harm Your computer and cannot be used to read any files or other data. Most web browsers accept cookies as a default. However, You can configure Your browser to prevent cookies from being placed on Your hard drive. Please note that should You choose to disable cookies some portions of the Site may not work properly. 

Clear Indexes may use cookies and other information for product development, new product research, Site enhancements and tracking Your Site usage and activity. For example, if You are a subscriber and haven't logged in or opened an email in 3 months, Clear Indexes may email or call You to check Your satisfaction. 

Lastly, we may collect IP addresses. An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to Your computer whenever You are navigating the Internet. Internet servers automatically identify Your computer by its IP address. 

**_Personal information_  
**  
We do not disclose any nonpublic personal information about You to anyone, except as permitted by law and as set forth below. The personal information Clear Indexes or its affiliates collect is used to protect Your confidential information, to verify your identity and ensure that only authorized Users have access to restricted data and reports. Personal information is also used to track and verify compliance with the Terms and Conditions applicable to the Site, as well as with federal, state and local laws. Clear Indexes will disclose or share Your personal information with a third party only as described in the most current version of this Privacy Policy, with Your permission to do so, or as required by law or regulation, court or administrative order, arbitral award or a governmental or regulatory authority or entity. In addition, we reserve the right to disclose any content, records or electronic communication of any kind, including without limitation personal information or private electronic communication transmitted on the Site: (i) to satisfy any law, regulation, or government request; (ii) if such disclosure is necessary to operate our business; or (iii) to protect the rights or property of Clear Indexes or its Users, sponsors, providers, licensors or merchants. We also reserve the right to reject any order or to request additional information from any User. 

**Information Clear Indexes Shares**

Clear Indexes may rent, but not sell, certain email address information of its free members ONLY to affiliates, marketers and third-parties for promotion and other purposes. We will not rent any email address of a Subscriber or asset management Client. 

**How Clear Indexes Protects Your Confidential Data**

Clear Indexes uses commercially reasonable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to maintain the confidentiality of Your information on the Site. The Site uses security measures to safeguard Your valuable data against loss, misuse and alteration while under our control. Our Site and servers are protected using encryption and other standard industry practices. We review and update web security and security procedures regularly. 

All data made available for download by Clear Indexes reside on a secure server and are encrypted. Although Clear Indexes exercises reasonable care to maintain the confidentiality of Your data, no transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure and we cannot guarantee that the personal information You submit to us will be free from unauthorized third party intrusion or interception. You therefore understand and agree that all information You submit to Clear Indexes or download from the Site is done so at Your own risk. 

**Clear Indexes Is Not Responsible For The Privacy Policies and Procedures Of Third Party Web Sites  
**  
You should be aware that when You are on the Site, You may be directed to other websites that Clear Indexes does not control. These other websites may send their own cookies, collect data or solicit personal information. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of third party websites. 

**Children**

Kids under 13: Do not send any information about yourself to us--including information such as your name, address, or e-mail address. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13. In the event that we learn we have collected any personal information from a child under the age of 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information from our database as quickly as possible. 

**Your Agreement**

By using our Site, You acknowledge and agree to this privacy policy. If You do not agree to any terms of this privacy policy, please do not use the Site. We reserve the right to change, add or remove all or part of our privacy policy at any time by posting the changes on this page. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to these terms means You accept such changes. 

If You have any comments or questions about our privacy policy, please contact us at the following addresses: 

505 Park Avenue, 2nd Floor   
New York, NY 10022   
  or   
[info@ClearAM.com](mailto:info@ClearAM.com) or   
call us at 1-866-641-5600 

COPYRIGHT © CLEAR INDEXES LLC. 2006. ALL RIGHTS RESERVED. 

Copyright in the pages and in the screens displaying the pages, and in the information and material therein and in their arrangement, is owned by CLEAR INDEXES LLC unless otherwise indicated.
